plugrush.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy | PlugRush Advertising Network

Our Privacy Policy describes how PlugRush (owned and operated by JMT Nordic AS) collects and uses the Personal Information you provide (automatically and/or manually) by using the PlugRush Platform. It also describes the options regarding our use of your personal information, how you can access it and how you can update it.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

This Privacy Policy outlines the basis of how any Personal Information we gather or that you give us, will be processed and treated by us. You hold the right to your Personal Information. It’s important for us that you read this information carefully.

For each client in the system, we may collect Personal Information like:

  * Username, password, email address
  * Personal id, name, address, phone number, Skype
  * Company id, name, address
  * Bank account number, Paxum/PayPal account email
  * IP address, user agent stings

This info is used for tasks including (but not limited to) administering your account, providing customer service, fulfilling orders, provide documentation, marketing/newsletters, do research and analysis. Your Personal Information is collected in order for us to fulfill our agreement with you as stated in our Terms of Service.

Marketing emails/newsletters from us are opt-in. System emails about your account and its activity is opt-out. You may change any of these preferences in your account at any time.

To have an overview of the Personal Information we hold for your account, please contact PlugRush Support and we will provide it as soon as possible.

#### GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)

25th May 2018 a new European law called The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) has come into effect. The purpose for this law is to give customers choice in how they are contacted by service providers and how their data is used. Our Privacy Policy has been updated to comply with these new regulations.

PlugRush is both the collector and controller of the personal data. PlugRush will only collect the data that is needed to fulfill the Agreement with you, as stated in our Terms of Service. The data will only be held for as long as required by Norwegian Law. You have the full right for insight in the Personal Information we have for your account. You have also the right to “be forgotten” as long as this is not in conflict with Norwegian Laws. Please contact our Data Protection Officer at dpo@plugrush.com if have any questions or have any requests.

#### Third-parties GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)

#### Sharing of Personal Information

We do not transfer or sell your Personal Information to third parties. However, we will share parts of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, for the basis of fulfilling our Agreement with you as stated in our Terms of Service.

We may share your Personal Information in cases were we believe in good faith it is necessary, such as respond to an investigation, a court request, investigate fraud, protect the safety of you, others or PlugRush.

#### Modification of Personal Information

It’s important to keep your Personal Information up-to-date at all times to ensure that we can provide you our services. You may do this directly in your account on our Platform or by contacting us. Should you want to cancel your account, you may contact us and we’ll close it for you. The Personal Information will be kept for as long as laws and regulations so require and afterwards deleted.

#### Payment Processors

We use DNB Bank ASA, Paxum, PayPal and SecurionPay for processing funds in and/or out of your account. We share some personal information with them in order to fulfill your load/withdrawal requests. Credit cards are not stored in PlugRush. For more information, please visit their respective websites.

[SecurionPay](https://securionpay.com/) / [WireCard AG](https://www.wirecardbank.com/)

#### Cookies

A cookie is a text file that is stored by a website on a users’ computer. We use them to keep you logged into our system (Session cookie) and for record keeping (Persistent cookie). Your Personal Information is not kept in cookies.

PlugRush may implement third-party services into our website and our Privacy Policy does not cover their use of cookies.

#### Security

At PlugRush, we follow industry standards for the safety of your Personal Information and all transmission in our Platform is secured with SSL.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Should there be any changes in our practices of collecting, using or sharing Personal Information, we will update this Privacy Policy accordingly. We recommend that you periodically review our Privacy Policy for changes. Should there be any substantial updates, we will inform of them on our website prior to the changes to become effective.
